Guide to the Emilie F. Miller papers, 1987-1991
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
  - Registrar's (Listing), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Republican Party, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Resource Mothers Program, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Resume- Original Copies, 1979-1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Resumes 1, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Resumes 2, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Resumes 3, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Resumes 4, 1981-1987 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Reverend Creedon- Social Worker of the Year, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Richmond (Repost), 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Richmond City Help Traffic, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - "Richmond Letter", July 25, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Richmond Visits, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Right to Work, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Road Allocation- Fairfax County, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Charles Robb- Senate Race and Governor of Virginia, 1981-1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Robb Lectures, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Charles Robb- Senate, 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Rotary Club, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Route 123 Improvement Project, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Route 28 Groundbreaking Project 1988-1990, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Route 58- Contract and Studies, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Sales Tax, September 19, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - School-Based Sex Clinics, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - School Bus Uses, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Science Education Policies for National Survival, November 14, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Scott Silverthorne- Correspondence, February 12, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Scouts-Boy Scouts Organization, February 17, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Senate Democratic Caucus, 1980s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Senator Dick Saslaw, 1984-1989 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Senate Page- Resolution and Application, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Senate Page Selection, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Senate Pages, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Senate Tracking Forms, 1980s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Senior Citizens, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Sensible Washington Area Transportation Coalition, February 15, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Sexual Assault Report, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - International Council of Shopping Centers, June 4 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sidewalk Repairs, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Singleton for Sheriff Campaign, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Small Claims Court, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Smart Card International, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Snow Removal, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Social Center, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Social Security Historical Data, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Social Services, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Southern Legislative Conference 1, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Southern Legislative Conference 2, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Southern Legislative Conference 3, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Southern Legislative Conference, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Southern Legislative Conference Committee on Human Resources, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Southern Legislative Conference, August 20-25, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Southern Legislative Summit- Healthy Infants and Families, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Space Activities, 1980s-1990s (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Speeches and Testimony 1, 1987-1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Speeches and Testimony 2, 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and Testimony- Central Fairfax Chamber, 1980s-1990s (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Speeches and Testimony: Commission on Educational Opportunity for all Virginians, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Speeches and Testimony- Disabled Veterans, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony- Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Speeches and Testimony- Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse, July 26. 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Speeches and Testimony- Taxes, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Speeches- Budget and Forecasting, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Speeches and Testimony- Volunteers, September 25, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Speeches- Highlights of the Comprehensive State Plan for Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse Services, December 15, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Senate Resolution for Board Nomination, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Spotlight on the Arts, 1987-1991 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Springfield Bypass- Newsclipping, May 6, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Saint Ambrose Church, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - State Mental Health and Mental Retardation Board Resignation Letter, January 11, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - State Bug- House Bill 1519, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Standards of Care House Bill 1077 (Carried Over), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - State Flower- Dogwood, 1980s-1990s (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - SCAN- Stop Child Abuse Now, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Straight, Incorporated Drug Treatment Program, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Surrogate Motherhood, 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Sydni Ann Shollenberger-Public Relations Resume, August 30, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Fairfax City- Oil Tank Farm Correspondences, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Fairfax City- Tank Farm Leak 1, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Fairfax City- Tank Farm Leak 2, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax City- Tank Farm Leak 3, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Taxes- State and Local 1, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Taxes- State and Local 2, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Virginia State Taxes, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Taxpayers Association, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Teen Health Center, February 22, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Teen Pregnancy, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Teen Suicide, 1980s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Term Limitation, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Mary Sue Terry, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Jefferson High School, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Timberlane Elementary School, March 8, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Tobacco Company, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Toll Road Corporation of Virginia, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Tort Reform (Correspondence), 1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Tourism, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Town Meeting, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Transfer Tax 1, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Transfer Tax 2, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Transportation 1, 1987-1991 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Transportation 2, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Transportation Pledge Bonds, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Trucks, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - TRW Federal Systems Group, August 18, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Tuition Assistance-Newsclipping, April 11, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Twenty-First Century Vision- System of Higher Education in Virginia, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Tytram- Tysons Transportation Association, 1987-1990 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - United Airlines- Facility Location Dulles Airport, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists- Voter Information, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Vanguard Services Unlimited- Demeter House, 1980s-1990s (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Vegetation Control Act, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Veterans, 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Victim Assistance- Virginia Network, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program, 1980s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Virginia-American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Labor, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Association for the Deaf, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Association of Community Services Board- VACSB, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Association of Consumer Affairs Administration, December 3, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Association of Female Executives- VAFE, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Association of Marriage and Family Therapy, 1980s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Association of Realtors, May 14, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Citizens Consumer Council, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Citizens for a Sound Economy, January 15, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Commission for the Arts, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Community Colleges, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Council of Human Rights, July 1, 1988 V (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Cultural Laureate, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center (WWRC), 1988 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Woodson High School, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance- Information Packet, 1985-1988 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Workman's Compensation, circa 1990 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Young Democrats, March 29, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Youth for Tomorrow, 1986-1990 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Youth Services Commission, December 28, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Zip Codes, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Department of Youth Services, January 10, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Education Association, January 2, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Education Financing, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Federation of Parents for Drug-Free Youth, 1980s-1990s (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Firearms Dealers Association, January 11, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Forestry/Forest Products Legislative Council, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Gasoline/ Automobile Repair Association, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Governmental Employees Association, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Historical Society, May 13, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Homecare Alliance, September 15, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Hospital Association, March 10, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Inland Ports, 1980s-1990s (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Liaison Office, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History, September 5, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Perinatal Association, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Petroleum Council Requirements for Fed. Drivers, December 7, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Power, August 1, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Retail Merchants Association, 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Retirement System, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Review, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Virginia School Board Associations, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Service Station Dealers, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Silver Star Foundation, 1980s-1990s (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Virginia School Bus Association, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Small Business Financing Authority, March 19, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Virginia State Police Association, July 10, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System Annual Report, June 30, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Taxpayers Association, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Treatment Center for Children, 1988-1991 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Water Project, Incorporated, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Women Attorneys Association, 1987-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Women's Network, 1988-1991 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Organization to Keep Abortion Legal- VOKAL, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Volunteers- Department of Voluntarism, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Voter Fraud- Electoral Board, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Voter Registration, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Washington Gas Light Company Annual Report, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Waste Management, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Waste Mana, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Waste Management- Recycling Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Waste Management- Waste Issues, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Water, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Welfare and Social Services, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Governor Wilder 1, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Governor Wilder 2, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Will, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - William and Mary College, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Earle C. Williams, July 4, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Williamsburg Commemorative Session, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Senate Bill 657- Wine Franchise Act, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - WNVT and WNVC- Local Television, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Congressman Frank Wolf, 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Women in the General Assembly, 1980s-1990s (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Council on the State of Women, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Women's Campaign fund 1988-1990, circa 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Women's Center, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Women's Equity Action League, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Women's Issues, 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - WETA, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Women's Issues 1, 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Women's Issues 2, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Women's Issues 3, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Women's Issues 4, 1985-1995 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Women's Issues, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Women's Roundtable 1, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Women's Roundtable 2, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Women's Roundtable 3, 1986-1989 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Women's Issues- Organizations, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Women's Lobbying Group, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Woodrow Wilson Bridge Improvement, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Establishment of Woodrow Wilson College, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Business- Higher Education Forum, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics 1, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics 2, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Center for Women and American Politics Forum for Women State Legislators, November 14-17, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Stationery, 1980s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Democratic Committee Platform Hearings 1, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Democratic Committee Platform Hearings 2, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Committee Platform Hearings 3, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Committee Platform Hearings 4, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives- Abortion, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Global Leaders for the South, 1989-1992 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Global Leaders for the South- A Bellsworth Leadership Forum 1, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Global Leaders for the South- A Bellsworth Leadership Forum 2, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Global Leaders for the South, Washington, D.C., November 8-10, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Global Leaders for the South, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Global Leaders for the South, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Global Leaders for the South 1, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Global Leaders for the South 2, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Global Leaders for the South, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Global Leaders for the South, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Global Leaders for the South- Alumni Directory, 1990s (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Council on Adolescent Pregnancy, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Conference, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Mental Health/Mental Retardation Conference List, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Office Copy Sign and Papers, 1980s-1990s (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Human Services Committee- National Conference of State Legislatures State-Federal Assembly, May 17-19, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Human Services Committee- National Conference of State Legislatures State-Federal Assembly, May 17-19, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Medical Research, 1984-1991 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Labor Issues 1, November 29-December 2, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Labor Issues 2, November 29-December 2, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Quest for Success, 1987-1989 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Report of the Commission on the Skills of the American Workforce, June 1991 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Southeast United States-Korea Joint Economic Conference, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Southern Growth, 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Southern Legislature Conference Human Resources Committee Business Meeting 1, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Southern Legislature Conference Human Resources Committee Business Meeting 2, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - 1990 State of States Symposium- Charlottesville, Virginia 1, December 6-7, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 1990 State of States Symposium- Charlottesville, Virginia 2, December 6-7, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Taking Charge of America's Future, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - The Impact of Women in Public Office, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Women's Campaign Fund- Strategic Leadership '90- Harvard, October 12-14, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Women's Campaign Research Fund- Strategic Leadership Conference, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Women's Campaign Research Fund, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - 18th Statewide Conference Department of Mental Health/Mental Retardation, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - St. Petersburg Trip Report, June 3-9, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Report of the Dialogues and Programs of the INET Foundation in Russia, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - 1990 Virginia Inauguration (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Women's Research Institute- Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Women's Research Institute- Virginia Polytechnic Institute 2, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Maryland Project for Women and Politics 1, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Maryland Project for Women and Politics 1, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Maryland Center for Women and Politics 3, 1986-1990 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Budget Amendments, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 1991 Budget Bill and Spreadsheet 1 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - 1991 Budget Bill and Spreadsheet 2 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - 1991 Budget Bill and Spreadsheet 3 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 1991 Budget Bill and Spreadsheet 4 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 1991 Budget Bill and Spreadsheet 5 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1991 Budget Bill and Spreadsheet 6 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Chief Patron Reports 1, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Chief Patron Reports 2, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Chief Patron Reports 3, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Chief Patron Reports 4, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Conference Committee Reports- House Bills, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 1991 Conference Committee Reports Senate Bills (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Education and Health- Higher Education Subcommittee 1, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Education and Health-Higher Education Subcommittee 2, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Education and Health Committee Senate Joint Resolution 63, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Education and Health Committee Senate Joint Resolution 99, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Education and Health Committee Elementary School Guidance Counselors, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Fairfax City Requested Budget Amendment, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors Legislative Tracking, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Fairfax County Public Schools Legislative Report, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Future Legislative Proposals, 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - 1989 General Assembly (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - 1990 General Assembly (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - General Assembly Legislative Services Policy, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - General Laws Committee 1, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - General Laws Committee 2, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Higher Education Council Legislative Tracking, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Local Government Committee 1, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Local Government Committee 2, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Miller Record, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Miller Record Pre-1987, 1978-1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Miller Record Correspondence 1, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Miller Record Correspondence 2, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Miller Record Correspondence 3, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Miller Record Correspondence 4, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials 1, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials 2, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials 3, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials 5, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials 6, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials 7, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials 8, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Oath of Office, January 13, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Health Planning Bill, January 23, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Records 1, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Records 2, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Records 3, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Records 4, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Records 5, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Records 6, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Restroom- Lounge for Women Senators, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bill 173- Federal Retirees Tax Exemption, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Senate Guidelines for Conference Attendance, 1986-1991 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Senate Matters, 1983-1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Senate-Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - 1990 Southern Governors Conference on Infant Mortality 1 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - 1990 Southern Governors Conference on Infant Mortality 2 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - 1990 Southern Governors Conference on Infant Mortality 3 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - 1988 Votes (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 1991 Votes (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Miller Record 1990s (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Acupuncture Correspondence, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Arts Funding 1, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Arts Funding 2, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Arts Funding 3, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Arts Funding 4, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Arts Funding 5, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Arts Funding 6, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Arts Funding 7, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Budget Cuts and Funding, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Senate Bill 503- Statute of Limitations/Child Abuse Extension Act, 1988-1991 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- Northern Virginia Public Hearing, January 5, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, January 10-17, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, January 18-24, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, January 25-29, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, January 30-31, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, February 1-12, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, February 13-19, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, February 21-23, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Dental Hygienists, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Elected School Boards Grievance Procedure, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Fair Elections Practices Correspondence, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, January 1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, February 1991 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Gun Legislation, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - House Bill 541- Funding for Circuit Support Services, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - House Bill 1308- Asset Forfeiture Sharing, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - House Bill 335- Insurance Correspondence 1, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - House Bill 335- Insurance Correspondence 2, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - House Bill 335- Insurance Correspondence 3, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - House Bill 1273- Local Zoning Restrictions on Rehabilitation Centers, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - House Bill 315 Malpractice Cap Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Mechanics Lien Laws Correspondence 1, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Mechanics Lien Laws Correspondence 2, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Substance Abuse Services Funding Correspondence, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Off-Track Betting Correspondence, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Senate Bill 235- Oopen Supply/Divorcement Correspondence Senate Bill 812, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Parental Notification Correspondence, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Physical Therapy- Direct Access, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 7)